[Music]
it's crazy to scratch their whole works
mr. dirty word
[Music]
is your man
it's not a cow it was supposed to be a
cat it's even worse I'm writing letters
friendships are important shin we need
to keep in touch with the people we care
about it shows they're appreciated
that's deep
I bet someone you appreciate someone who
cooks your meals cleans your clothes and
loves her little boy very very much
anyone spring to mind what are you doing
here says we should touch the people we
know I'm here to touch you coming
through
oh wait a minute don't worry I'll just
make myself at home
whoa where's my room give me a break I'm
on vacation if principal Enzo knew about
this you think he'd trust you with our
impression of little minds
I think it's a grief you gave me for
stuff and melted cheese in my cubby but
I didn't tell the principal did i right
cuz we're buddies right don't look at me
like that
geez you're worse than my mother what
are you doing here anyway
huh well I I felt bad for you you're all
alone I I thought you two want some
company
really oh that's sweet but how come a
girl like you doesn't have a boyfriend
well actually there is someone I was
hoping he'd call this weekend but he
hasn't yet news flash
here's why you still play with toys what
are you for keep your paws off my puppy
so how's your vacation going well ho-bag
off says you're getting a little
personal what was I thinking hmm good
news I've decided to stay overnight no
no no no no no no no no why not I'm
uglier than puffy sighs my mom says it's
okay huh I think it's time to give your
mother a call story how are you huh
shins with you yes and he mentioned
something about spending the night but
oh that kid I'm sorry he must be driving
you crazy not at all I love having my
students visit really huh I'll pick him
up in the morning you guys have a great
time now
[Music]
louder I'll just order up a load of junk
food keep busy on the other hand do I
really want to see what this kids like
on this sugar high
shin-chan what do you want for dinner
huh shout the Victoria's treasures my
dad gets the catalog says he just reads
it for the articles where I buy my
underwear is none of your business
that's yes stop
lots of drawers over here get this
straight no one's allowed in my drawers
another reason you're still single
shin-chan
if you don't behave yourself I'm gonna
send you right home oh come on you need
me around for practice you know you
might have a kid like me someday ever
think that's why I'm still single
[Music]
actually I was hoping
hey guess waiting for a bath here just a
sec darn I thought I had an extra
toothbrush you need to brush your teeth
before their baby teeth they're gonna
fall out anyway can you don't want
to get cavities know what the drug
stores right downstairs I'll go buy one
for you Janeiro I'm busy what are you Oh
[Music]
sometimes I do every now and then but
it's not much of a problem why is some
guy called said his name was sticky icky
sticky Ricky
whatever real nosy too wanted to know
who I was and then he's all like whoo
sorry must have got number wrong and I'm
like don't tell me your problems I'm
watching TV okay dude don't worry he
won't call back
watch my ears that's why there's so much
wax I could stick a wick in your head
and light you up like a jack-o'-lantern
dad come on how'd I know I was your
boyfriend he's not he's just a very nice
guy we met at the carnival he won my
teddy bear for me Buffy you should keep
it back look it's not even waterproof
oh chin it can be quite a handful I
really do love him yeah it would be nice
to have one mine someday
[Music]
this won't get away this time she's
gonna make a sale
I've sold every sucker on my beat the
baby book by rinky-dink except those
miserable two eras but do i ha they
don't call me hunt them down easy for
nothing focus he she this is for the
100% sales record and the year's supply
of corn pads don't let this kid blow it
like last time kid I could have made
division manager if I hadn't been
arrested well that's not gonna happen
this time
[Music]
well I guess you can go none of the
mental hospitals reported a missing
patient I'm sure you realize why we had
to check one month yeah that'll look
great on my resume it's the kid books
just for you
the he-she my name is a she miss hey she
tell your mama I want to see her okay
she doesn't let strange men in the house
I'm not a man lady just like your mom
watch Jack talk my limes no lady hmm
true now that I think about it
[Music]
teller it was a misunderstanding I bet
she'll buy you a nice educational book
wouldn't that be swell look yeah there's
a bribe
she is that you dawn I can't find him
oh well isn't that just too bad so if I
help you find him you'll tell your mom
to buy some ring kidding huh shouldn't
be too hard unless the poor little
things been great
tell him his dog's dead why don't you
we'll find him don't you worry hunt him
down he sure is on the case huh what
[Music]
good idea I'll buy him a dog biscuit
cheese deluxe double layer with
strawberries Oh
better make it two he's hungry steel
I'll have to sell two books just to
break even
hey mister it's miss okay a just big
boned
whatever look this isn't working out
maybe look he's not coming cuz shutting
scaring them off that would be you
thanks for the cheesecake hey what the
little egg got me again Chuck no
customer gets away from hunt him down he
she
I'll try come with this found you lucky
[Music]
rock paper scissors
hey I let you lied now come to a laundry
[Music]
it's coming back to swear according to
this you should be right here
[Music]
okay short stuff I know you're right
here oh well you beat me again I know
all the tricks kid best in the business
but I finally met my match I'm off to
the hospital to get these ribs taped you
know kid your rinky-dink material if you
ever want to go into sales give a
call
[Music]
no I'm just missing a part geez mom
why'd you break our fan me you're the
one that broke it it'll take months for
my hair to grow back good thing I still
have this wig and when Schwindt I dyed
my hair what if I go crazy no good weed
sound I know let's buy an air
conditioner we can use the money we were
saving dissention to obedience school ha
ha ha obedience school but honey I
finally got the dog trainer to take you
we agreed it was our last hope get that
paper training myself I want that air
conditioner Oh sweetie bear this is so
important to me you're not gonna say no
to your little wifey are you watch your
fingers she's gonna fight we don't need
an air conditioner hon I'll fix the fan
right like it fixed the microwave every
time I use it now I glow for hours
[Music]
pretty good prices we could use a new
video camera I always wanted to be on TV
yeah dad it's a horror movie shin that's
not funny let's check out computers it's
a ticket to paradise your own private
vacation on naugahyde island relaxing
isn't it yes but what's that smell
[Music]
we should get shin a computer
I don't know Harry he'll just spill
something sticky on it he's a big boy
now he doesn't do stuff like that
anymore did you hear we are air
conditioners let's check it out no
impulse buys now let's take time and get
the right one hey this one's cool works
with a remote this one
yeah it'll cost you but trust me the
house will be cold not to hang meat it
how do you know so much about it
booze dad bought one you know the
janitor with a lazy eye oh great
so it's official every in town as
an air conditioner but us do you folks
need an air conditioner no we have one
do three actually we're just looking for
a spare don't like her she's loopy from
breaking our fan with her head now she's
all bald on one side little family
conference excuse us
let's check a sales catalog okay there's
a cheap one but it wouldn't last a week
well it's energy-efficient but I'm all
for that
can't go wrong with this baby folks this
year's model practically new previously
owned by a little old lady from Yokohama
hardly ever used said the wine reminded
her too much of her late husband seems
like a good deal not for a used one
can't you knock a little off the price
you don't know my boss if I knock off
the price he'll knock me off just to get
this thing over with I'll give you a
discount how about five bucks off this
one's cheaper
oh that's last year's model oh the one
you're trying to sell us will be cheaper
next year ah technically family
conference don't buy it
not until next year then it'll be last
year's model the favored buckle but it's
hot this year big deal it's just a
little late why do we need an air
conditioner anyway just fix the fan
well at least you spent the day in an
air-conditioned store if it's hot
tomorrow we'll go shopping for
microwaves you you guys stay here I'm
gonna go stand in the traffic
[Music]
[Applause]