[Music]
it's crazy
scratch their homework mr. dirty word
[Music]
the walking talking faster
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh baby my tanks are full that's what
you said last time and I woke up one
night to find you chewing on my leg
don't be silly you were just dreaming
you left teeth marks this time it'll be
different I'm following a strict
four-point plan one no midnight snacks
oh do when I do eat it's very small
portions right and what's free no more
between meal treats sure I'm gonna
exercise my butt off but not at some
expensive gym I'll just work extra hard
cleaning the house and lose weight for
free hey this might actually work I'm
proud of you mom
allow me to help well thanks all I had
was that one little piece think of it as
one lush belly roll right thanks a lot
round
bend down twist bend down and the house
is clean I'm a big exercise machine ma I
think you missed a spot
yeah where huh just look at my room
it's a Pigpen in here I cleaned your
room 10 minutes ago
you made this mastic jus yeah what's
your point yourself just trying to help
Mitch looks like those thunder thighs
could use a bigger workout oh well at
least now the house is spotless dragging
through a mud puddle oh and you might
want to check your bedroom that chili
dog I gave him showed up again so move
your feet up mamacita right honey bunny
my abs do need a workout boy hard work
really kills your appetite I'm not at
least bit hungry
Oh barbeque here what are you doing just
playing pretend
oh yeah pretend what pretend barbeque
boy where you got your honey smoked ribs
char-broil chicken
[Music]
nothing like to smell it grilled meat
you're on the planet you buy your 100
Ozen take a whip
this smells a hundred percent fat free
Mike are you doing it's just pretend
shin-chan please don't torture mommy I'm
trying to stick to my diet so can't you
play something else
anything else uh-huh anything you want
[Music]
peppermint pigouts monkey butt banana
don't play ice cream man evil suddenly
I'm a hungry for some reason you can fit
in your mouth at once
that'll keep them quiet I will not be
strong
[Music]
you okay honey
how's the diet going she's never gonna
stick to it all she thought about today
was food it's true I kept having these
crazy visions of barbecued ribs and ice
cream and maybe you should just give up
on this diet I want to lose at least 10
pounds
what for hon I think you've got a really
cute figure you should eat as much as
you want
oh don't tell her that she'll check your
plate your green peppers how generous I
know nice try but eat your own dinner
I'm still on a diet y-you don't have to
do it for me I like you big I can hear
you coming guys I need to do this for me
I promised myself I wouldn't quit so I
won't give up
[Music]
so I'm guessing the diets over better
she's the whole fridge than my leg
[Music]
listen up little people it's almost time
for the all-school Junior Olympics again
and I'm sick and tired of happy bunny
kitty garden getting its pants beat off
so we're gonna whip you bunnies in the
shade with a good old-fashioned military
workout who wants to sweat sweat what's
wrong with a Swedish sauna then we could
cool our parched little ropes iced cocoa
machine oh thank you brain freeze huh
huh following soldiers your first
mission is to take gas bridge
[Music]
I can hear you're holding up the whole
platoon this Ridge over to River Kwai
based on my calibrations this structure
is completely sound so there's no danger
at all if you stay in the middle and
don't like me you're right monkey boy I
don't like you okay junior commandos the
goal is to get past these pegs as
quickly as possible
[Music]
but you could change all that you have
got to stop watching those soaps what a
coincidence I'm known as Black Widow on
the web that's why no indeed sir they
eat their husbands you soldiers are not
what I call working to your full
potential I guess you need some
incentive what do I gotta do
maybe rough up your daddy's holy kid
here's my offer first kid to finish the
course gets a little something special
it's a trip to Hollywood where you'll
receive a lifetime supply of brainless
bikini babes courtesy of Jackie Jews
twice the sugar out the nutrition I
should have never gone into the witness
protection program okay just hold onto
the ring bow and swing across the water
here don't let go now
[Music]
Thanks go ahead so do it
here we go then go already now I'm some
kids will do anything for a lousy prom
hey I'm the one who will excuse you told
me what took you so long
let's see your leg Oh father it's fine
oh my senior still you said you were
hurt I just wanted to see if you'd save
me I wouldn't leave you out here alone I
brought it to buy gumballs
[Music]
gee so we all get a price just for
trigon fist alban looks like I'm the
only one who lost today just throw that
cheap outfit away trust me you haven't
lost much except my mind like a
troublemaker
going out to eat a mamacita I'm meeting
at Kay for coffee try not to blow up the
kitchen again while I'm gone hey they
should put a warning on soda cans do not
shake until fizzy and then heat in
microwave Oh dad's still sleeping better
wake him up so and keep an eye on you
while I'm gone
gotcha you know why are we here
something better for the next hour
your dad's problem so doctor child let
me stop you right there Bob there are no
problem children just problem adults
adults who don't understand that their
young son it's usually a boy in these
cases is simply trying to express
affection for them
[Music]
Oh Uli's Sonny Boy you deserve a reward
how's about Aika billion cha-cha-cha
with the official master trademark apply
bubble fun we're incorporating your
jockstrap sold separately from now on
nothing to eat but liver liver and
cereal liver in your lunch box sushi
looks like eyebrows
- Groucho Oh crazy citizen work way
better not I am so dead
[Music]
hi honey you should look in the mirror
give it to me straight
how bad is it it's well it's actually
[Music]
hey get a grip what the heck is so funny
I think you should borrow this you know
honey you look a lot better it's
unconventional but it does hide the
eyebrows so what do you think can I wear
it to work you said they made me look
better I do that's the problem I know
you can pretend your eyebrows burned off
when the kitchen exploded
sure we'll bandage you up say you took
some shrapnel from the shins Cola bonds
whoa
you're a genius mamacita yep I think we
got the problem covered well it's a
definite improvement over those glasses
huh
doesn't look too stupid no way you could
start a whole new trend a trend yeah bet
they'd browse the safe and easy face
piercing alternative so the guys at work
won't make fun of me no you sure right
right
I hope so cuz I hate when people laugh
at me don't worry what kind of person
would laugh at you yeah like totally
rude dude anybody want to play connect
the dots
[Music]
[Applause]