[Music]
scratch the dirty word
groceries are getting so expensive Shin
Chan's cookies even cheaper when you buy
them in the day-old bin so I could
splurge on these babies next time Harry
works tight at the office you and me got
a hot date better put him with a kid
can't find him you don't even say hello
to your mother yeah yeah later I smell
cookies give me give me give me oh so I
should reward you for being rude huh
took you five years to figure that out
do this do that you think I like being
talked to you like a dog what are you
doing
check it out I mean maybe you do like
being talked to like a dog ruff ruff I
get my cookies now you like bunnies can
whole wagonload with your name on them
[Music]
get mom I did everything you told me you
did huh
gargled did the bear boogie I didn't
tell you to do that
but do it in for free whatever go eat
your cookies remember ordering real
cookies without green mold growing on
them
[Music]
if I don't eat them can't sleep
starving no contest he won't find them
here I'm being watched
oh it's just a dog
[Music]
did you feel that earthquake hammer
shock it give you aftershock Oh Jan are
you up here what are you doing nothing
sweetie have you seen those new cookies
I bought cookies no cookies here haven't
seen no cookies oh uh Oh silly me I hid
them from you got something maybe a
tummy ache
coz you know your belly looks swollen
[Music]
must be for meeting your wonderful
cooking oh I doubt it especially since
you dumped you're playing the dog dish
when you think I'm not looking stand up
a minute honey bunny um right now
[Music]
[Laughter]
next time you want something just ask
don't go snooping around in my things
mom I just happened to see those cookies
I never snoop around in your stuff oh
I'm sorry honey I didn't mean to hurt
your feelings
he's still hungry yeah let's break out
the chunky cheese you hiding your under
draw why did I ever become a teacher
of course because I wanted to serve
children yeah I'd like to serve them
alright Boyle but the sign of four
five-year-olds are the worst they suck
the life right out of you why don't they
just grow up right on dude chin chin
nice surprise yeah Kitty gardeners grind
me down too I'd rather hang with an
older woman even a way older woman no
she provides Pizza tempting offer but I
just want to get home as soon as
possible
why what happened oh I get it
you stood you up again gee Sam I just
got a hurt stuck me up what are you
talking about your boyfriend
what do you dump you for a newer model
what boyfriend
I'm temporarily between boyfriend's okay
but trust me there's plenty of guys
interested in a gal like me yeah what's
your name maybe she could tell you what
you're doing wrong what's the point
Chinchin I think I hear your mother
calling time for his boat to head on
home
bye-bye so where do you live oh right
over no not there it's so not where I
live imagine me living in a dump like
that every school thinks you're
glamorous sophisticated
[Music]
you've been bragging about you never
invited me over
there's no room you are such a loser boy
find out the truth you look kind of
pasty I'll walk you home huh oh don't
bother
I feel great I'm going to pimp walk all
the way home
whoa bony butt and maybe that's why the
boyfriend dumped you how's that out
listen it's getting late don't you want
to take a nice warm bath and snuggle
into your PJs oh this this is so sorry
let's start a room you know you've
always been my favorite student I'm not
in your class maybe that's why but as
much as I'd love to have you walk home
with me I live way over those mountains
you know how far away that is yes I
believe the exact distance it's 52
kilometers you couldn't walk it plus the
range has an elevation of 10,000 feet
you need climbing gear and a Sherpa
guide to make it uh Cosmo I but she said
she was gonna power walk the whole way
oh she's putting you on big guy I've got
more extra credit projects to finish
those brownie points don't earn
themselves
Brainiac I got your brownie points right
here
[Music]
teachers lie I'm feeling my little
psyche brazing oh you thought I was
lying oh no I was just kidding of course
you can come home with me my TV's broken
though so you'll miss the mast muchacho
missed a masked one he's gone in half an
hour right right you'll never make it
home in time so if you need to hurry off
now I understand can you at least give
me your address
dress address hold up
see I'm not allowed to tell you it's an
unlisted address yeah
mentioned giuliana is Trey exclusive
manse young Giuliana you mean that yep
that's home sweet home excuse me I hear
my phone ringing bye hey I got time to
walk you to your door protect you I've
already got one
[Music]
me and binky will okay here's my final
offer I walk you home and give you a
nice crisp dollar to leave me alone buck
fifty and you got a deal
Donna and you gotta carry me I what
piggyback
my little legs are tired from chasing
you right well lucky needs a lift to he
got dragged most of the way yes fine I'm
not very comfortable
you got bony shoulders oh I'm so sorry
it's go any faster no well you're better
I'm gonna miss Matt from Joe Joe come on
horsy
dropped I am NOT going to what's wrong
you liked him yesterday and the day
before that's the problem
this rice is so old it's growing a beard
oh really
well I don't hear shin-chan complaining
sorry I brought it up oh no you don't
get off that easy you got a problem with
my cooking
you know I'd like steak every night -
but you're the one always telling me to
save money so I make sure we could
stretch every meal do we have to fight
in front of the kid okay I'm not
fighting Harry I'm just explaining why I
am right and you are wrong I refuse to
use Yeley voice at the table my mother
brought me up to be civilized
I'm so sorry I'm not more like your mom
maybe you should head on over there her
house for some of her greasy pl'anna you
Monica I won't sit here while you insult
my mother's cooking bench stand up cuz
I'm just getting started
that's it oh where are you going out for
dinner oh that's just great you're not
even taking your family well come if you
want I'm just going out back maybe the
dog left some kibble better than your
dressing what did you say real this it's
bigger
you can't miss what you like my cooking
don't you sure MA if I wasn't around
would you miss me watch she's image that
miss you like crazy really yeah I missed
the bus I had to walk to school oh so
basically I'm just a taxi service
no one appreciates me in this family
fine then maybe I should go away for a
while
someplace quiet just the place
screaming trolleys radial arcade
no I need to be alone I feel so
empty maybe I'm being oversensitive but
it seems like you guys don't care about
my feelings or listen to what I have to
say yeah whatever you're here whoa dad
what are you doing here um let's see I
live here we're right in front of our
house hey why is the door open
no one's home that's funny
I guess mom went out but it's not like
her to leave the door open
probably spying on the fat lady next
door she does the treadmill were nothing
but a Mets cap uh-huh thanks for the
mental picture how many times do I have
to tell you don't eat with dirty hands
huh kid what have you been doing rolling
in the dirt somebody sure needs a bath
yeah you do smell kind of funky
nice relaxing hey Mitzi throw some
towels she's not back yet where's Matt
is it about time she came in and spoil
their fun yeah
boy it's late you sure she didn't say
where she was going huh nope
now that you mention it yes she said
something about getting away from here
huh what what else did she say oh no one
appreciates me for so we got any
pretzels no way I think some of her
clothes are missing and where's her
person going for shoes dad you think one
run away well what do you think she'll
come back
actually chases a few cats eat some
garbage and wee-wees on all the
firelighters shin she's not a dog dog
smog that's what I do
I'm calling Kay that's probably where
she is over and her best friends
complaining about me
Hey hi it's me Harry your best friend's
husband could I speak to Mitzi she's not
there where is she you think she would
have clubbed maybe there's been a taxi
did you mean accident not when she's
driving she runs into those cabs on
purpose you stay here I'll be right back
Oh that's what they say in those scary
movies you were imagining things that
scary movies too
next thing you know some baby bird a
halter top is lunch
[Music]
you guys scared me scared you what are
you doing in there you fell asleep in
the closet well it's the one place I can
be by myself it's nice and peaceful in
there sometimes I just curl up on the
top shelf and in the closet weird oh
sorry
I'm hungry meet Jim so am i I'm guessing
no one wants leftovers given to the dog
who wants to go to burger barn
you guys were really worried yeah around
8 o'clock I realize you were missing I
was in the closet all day and you didn't
even notice I was gone
[Music]
[Applause]