[Music]
Oh works
[Applause]
[Music]
just as
talking
[Music]
well it is a business trip exactly
which means the wife and kid are back in
cousin city let's hit some hot spot yeah
I don't think mitt seed like this so
don't tell her my wife
boolie she'd throw a clot if she knew
what I did on these trips Oh what do you
do let's just say I Dinis almost curious
huh we need to go grocery shopping for
dinner come on dad will be home from
work any minute
you got old-timers disease for days if
he comes back at all of course you will
this mess your crummy housekeeper mix
hey hey you made this mess these are
your toys oh that's a lame excuse I sure
do miss him don't you
[Music]
I bet he misses us just as much it's
almost too good to be true I can party
with the guys and Mitzie you'll never
know she'll think I'm working away at my
dad's I can do them I wish I brought
more cash oh well I'll max out the old
credit card shut out uh Master muchacho
trading card please get there hey let's
go out for dinner out grease patty
speaking of someplace and where the
heck's my credit card hmm this will help
us forget how much we miss dad whoo
where we getting the money for this
don't worry about it honey dad's paying
before he left I borrowed his credit
card you'll never miss it Wow it's Danny
way to go what's a credit card
well you give it to someone instead of
cash and then you get something back Oh
like my trading cards
well kind of watch what happens when I
give it to the waiter here we are Bank
of psycho robotic Oh what's this doing
here
[Music]
she took the credit card now she's out
spending money she Chan did you take
dad's card from my wallet no you took
that one from here I treated him when he
wasn't looking
here's cheesy plastic card for to him
nah that's not a fair trade
Oh tell me that mass muchacha had six
fingers
shin where's dad's card Oh looky it's
shaving my underpants here Eagle aren't
you feeling poor boy
[Music]
this is great just the two of us like
before we were married
[Music]
[Applause]
police board he's armed and dangerous
oh my gosh thanks for bailing us out no
problem but why didn't you just call
Harry he's out of town oh well if you're
lonely come hang at our house
really why not I'm already hanging here
that's Willowby Nara will save you a
seat near the jello bit right I see
there I hope it wasn't our place that
got robbed
I'll just make sure the family's okay
then fun Club here I come
[Music]
like back in high school
hey I've got two cheesecakes sitting in
the freezer let's go over to our house
I'm with you kid pig out Barney well at
least the answering machine wasn't
stolen
[Laughter]
that's just Lance calling summer but
she's probably not gonna answer cuz
she'll find out he's the father of
Laurel is half sister's baby I told you
not to watch those soaps Lance
something's wrong Mitzi
shin-chan if something's happened to my
family huh
Mitzi is that you hey I'm a family man
bub and I'm goin home
if I hurry I can get your last train to
Kazu I said I'm not coming you sleaze
monkey honey huh Mitzi sweet xiu'er and
you probably haven't noticed but your
credit cards missing but don't worry
lucky has it you too bear are you crying
TV
[Music]
guess somebody's right yes credit card
shinstr you're catching liar liar you
can't catch my butt unless you actually
turn who cares about here it keeps bus
crash you have to catch her I'm over
tightened your have a tight end in
baseball you do if you got this book
rash baby swings big kids push us you're
on no way we'll play wherever we want
where are we a bunch of wimps Mama's
boys yeah pretty much
[Music]
you spit on it you're just cleaning it
for you I had it in my pocket with a
green bologna sandwich I'll boil my
hands later here it comes
[Music]
I call it yeah all you hit was
somebody's dog sport
oh let's run the old guy that has real
mean really they called him the kids are
later what
but he's got the bat I'm not going after
it it's not like that no oh then you're
dead meat you're the one who threw it
now go get it whoa got a run time from a
sunburn lessons she did and tell the
truth oh wait did I get my hands on some
whiny little kid I bet our mask you mean
to kid German French braid Aziz and grab
him by his belly button and slingshot a
little pop to the moon let's lie go get
your bat chicken I'm not a chicken I
just want to live to see my sixth
birthday let's go get your booboo Barney
okay then let's forget it
who needs that dumb bat anyway he's gone
I'll get it
[Music]
that bad for kid grins I'm from the
Department of animal regulation yeah put
a leash on those goldfish look like the
bike surprise women call yourself a cop
but I'm the one who bites
is this your bat so you didn't come here
to do that yeah but it's not mine it was
an accident I only threw the bat kid who
threw it
Jovan your daughter's is the wrong guy
Georgie's compared to my mom's oh this
is the kid that being your
[Music]
I said we should teach you a lesson
yeah nice try but home was a girl with a
name like Homer hey calm down
[Music]
sorry mister
can I have my ball back your body
[Music]
chicken on a plan
next time the Tooth Fairy comes I
pretend I'm one too then we frolic in
the night I knock her out rollers of
course you want it oh no thanks I gotta
go mail a letter Oh your mom's got a
crush on your story well card for my
grandma she keep go faster somebody sent
her a love letter well anyway my mom's
certified mail this she'll buy me a bike
I could let you have my old trike real
cheap it's still a little rusty from
riding it in the bathtub
but Belle works no thanks moths get me a
new two wheeler just for helping out
whoa well gotta go see ya see if I got
this straight
Oh your mom get a present why didn't you
tell me sooner
[Music]
you love me mamacita look is good enough
to eat ah I'm going shopping
the keys in Lucky's doghouse be a good
boy now bye bye
[Music]
well you're safe there mom's gotta stop
hiding you dish looks like the mixer had
a little snack attack have to meet nod
bones good thing I was in here she'd eat
meat too well I hope she gets back soon
cuz how can I help her if you need me
here
yeah shin-chan darling you cleaned the
house all by yourself you got it babe oh
you're such a good boy like you're
should not go unrewarded Oh Mike won't
be necessary important I could use a car
you got it
and let's fill that trunk with your
favorite tooth rotting snack all falling
out - could come to your heart's content
on junior chunky shirt yes and since all
that sugar will destroy your bones and
you for life watching you help your mom
[Music]
whoa a really nasty man I should please
mr. oh don't you make a mess scared them
off when the Sardar to undress ohh ohh
Thank You Sheena chair Mama's brave
little boy now I'll take you to the
store and buy a new toy hi I'm home have
you been behaving yourself look I
brought you some cake where are you
[Music]
I moved to Guam hiding from mommy
whatever come with me I've got something
special for you
[Music]
[Applause]