[Music]
scratch the dirty word
talking
[Music]
tomorrow we leave for vacation right
cool as we all know vacations are
supposed to be relaxing but we never get
to relax do we because when we're
halfway to the airport we remember we
left the iron on or the water running or
the dog in the dryer thank you very much
chin chin mmm-hmm
so I told you we didn't have to go back
for him he'd already chewed his way out
through the lint trap my point is this
time we're gonna be organized I'm all
over it honey gas valves turn off
windows locked alarm clock wound and set
for oh six hundred bags ready to roll
and the door oh you can stay without
mrs. goober you have more fun in the
dryer
see huh my gosh it's hard to believe but
this time we might actually have a
relaxed normal vacation yo Mitch back
your fat pants we can use them for a pup
tent okay forget normal but anyway it's
time to begin operation vacation
we just want to show you when that alarm
goes off its a.m. everybody up okay okay
we got it worried over sleep I don't
have time to spell it out for you just
do what you do every morning just pull
your pants down and do the bare butt
boogie we're just gonna relax and enjoy
ourselves thanks again let's go okay
when we get to the airport have the
tickets out
[Music]
[Applause]
well we didn't miss the train so we'll
make our flight we're sure cutting it
close though
so where's it's right
[Music]
ah not too bad only 15 minutes behind
schedule
whoa I'm got this creepy feeling I'm
being watched
sorry it's regular okay team when we get
to the shuttle station move fast hit the
platform running and grab the first
shuttle train you see it's gonna take
teamwork so stay alert and be ready to
move on my signal would be yes
[Applause]
[Music]
yes but you know what you have to do
right yes sir I gotta stay focused but
I've gotta be fast and I've gotta go
wee-wee not no head for the ticket
counter target in sight
[Music]
to catch a plane remember you can lick
each other's necks on your own time so
far it's been great
jeez we all go away cause of them I hope
they have the decency to be embarrassed
you should have told mom you put chicken
wire in her pocket okay
I kind of liked being patted down oh we
made it but the good time begins
[Music]
[Applause]
okay don't start acting like a jackass
remember you're a married man willpower
will better look somewhere else look at
something don't raise your voice in
public daddy and I will discuss this
later
yeah that's where we're going geez Sam
it's it's weenie
now wash glass bigger net it only looks
small cuz we're miles away as you get
closer you'll see it's absolutely
enormous Oh like mom's keister a lot
different than Kazu City right gang okay
let's see what this town has to offer
what she will do first oh gosh should we
go swimming or boating or fishing er I'm
just dying to see the Art Museum and
maybe do some shopping and who kitty but
we're gonna need a lot of energy for all
that we better get something to eat
first
this town's right on the ocean the sea
we must be great so let's get some fish
we could get but honey they're famous
for their pea soup
so what get some cans to take home with
you why when I can eat it right here
where it's fresh weak you sure isn't
fresh berry fish is fresh we're eating
fish Millie I didn't come to pea soup
gathered on the world just to eat a
greasy fat fried ham
[Music]
that's the problem now it's my turn
I want pea soup here it is world-famous
PTIN beets
Wow the guidebook gives it two forks up
guess it's a good place to eat good
place to eat you guys are sick just
relax
hi you must be beat painted here I'm
Pete what'll it be
let's see small pea soup medium pea soup
large pea soup three large bowls of some
hot nourishing pea soup special order at
the wind I have some for security with
the side of garlic bread don't have that
here vanilla flan that either shin it's
a pea soup restaurant they serve pea
soup you're not gonna see vanilla flan
in a place like this
[Music]
what do you know one vanilla flan you
have it don't you
now just to picked you okay now it's my
turn
let's go for some nice fresh seafood you
can't still be hungry sure she can have
seen her swallow a pot roast hole oh
very funny
look you guys ate where you wanted now I
get to pick a restaurant
oh but mitts we're full of hamburgers
and pea soup will explode you've got
some nerve Harry no Hara
you don't have a problem taking your fat
cat clients out to fancy high-priced
restaurants so while your wife sits
alone eating cold noodle yes right okay
honey honey
I guess what I want isn't very important
to you
think only of yourself I guess I'll just
starve to death
but at least father's warm and well fed
her husband's a peg she should sue all
right all right I was selfish have some
shellfish clam kebabs our babe us
pigeons also eat sake truce if you don't
got any just squid fritters were great
[Music]
and a chocolate fudge malted after all
we're here to have fun I mean we're on
vacation right right right right
so let's go eat
[Music]
gross overeating and I do mean gross
you'd better stay here tonight for
observation your squid fritters it was
your lousy pea soup
I want my flan you're welcome enjoy the
rest of your vacation just don't eat
yourself to death I can't believe we
spent the first night of our vacation in
the hospital gross overeating I've never
been so humiliated I think it's a taste
of shame out of your mouth like
breakfast at burger barn
Oh mother double fried grease patty
let's just pick up a rent-a-car and go
for a nice quiet drive okay now where's
that place I called let's see ah there
it is right over there it's the best we
can do in our budget I I'm sure it's
fine
[Music]
I'm I'm chilly - it's like bowl knocker
in here the air conditioners stuck on hi
oh excuse the mask
I lost my nose from frostbite why don't
you fix the air conditioning doesn't
cost money
why hit something fixed when it's
cheaper to let it rot that's my motto
Oh your rental cars ready Harry this
cars a piece of junk it's fine might be
helpful stick your legs through the hole
and run go faster oh just because I got
a bargain
relax look at the view whew it's just a
long empty road
[Music]
look how fast they're going boy that's
the way to travel
[Music]
no son I'm going to obey the speed limit
besides it gives you a chance to enjoy
the scenery something's wrong
the darn cars dying oh I know it you got
a gray cloud on this thing if you wanted
a planter no I don't know what went
wrong I do you were too cheap to spring
for a real car maybe we were carrying
too much weight
Oh my fat butt broke it huh blame your
father's bad head he's the one who
rented this can opener from that
noseless nut ball in the first place
oh so I'm a Fathead at least you got
that right it's your fault we couldn't
spend more for a car you blew our budget
on that fancy hotel
so you're the fat mm-hmm actually hers
is kind of quick we never even stayed at
the hotel we had to sleep at the
hospital because you made a pig of
yourself oh yeah
I know you eating with both boots porky
you wanna kill my appetite
let's get a whiff of your stanky foot
fungus
[Music]
I'm sorry are you avoid scare you
your head what our heads I never notice
their shapes before they're like totally
weird
forget saving for my college fund I'll
need to know for plastic surgery
Oh give you surgery smart guy
good-looking ectomy alright alright
already let's just contact Julie and
have her send a tow truck for us well I
hope you brought a Ouija board cuz
there's no phone out here
I don't even see a house no it's real
[Music]
Rose Wow our car broke down we need it
don't let the word head scare you
they're not really
aliens well one is it I live just up the
road to peace you cobbler
when I tell you about picking up
weird-looking strangers he's been out in
the Sun too long our car broke down
could we use your phone I reckon so
follow me young fella Thanks wanna see
my friend I'm too young but thanks for
the offer
you're funny young it so you're a real
farmer's daughter huh
I read all about you in that play Phil a
joke book dad hides behind the toilet
look real live cows aren't they
sweet hmm lanes bright we're always out
of milk okay just shut your piehole
mister Jilly won't answer the phone and
I can't get another rental until
tomorrow
y'all can stay here tonight there's room
at the bar did you say Barnes right
Cuffy now that we got that snake problem
licked I think we can think of imposing
oh you can pay us back help milk the
cows stop the hogs gutting chickens for
supper
we're city folk not exactly cut out for
farm life well yeah it sure does take
today he's out of our hair woman let's
go get us some chicken hard work yeah I
think shins getting a real taste of life
on a farm
[Music]
[Applause]