[Music]
in the rules
as a steam engine just ask
but he's a walking talking blue
[Music]
[Applause]
incredibly beautiful model / mommy I'm
the dad mild-mannered accountant by day
but at night oh mighty superhero and
sensible dinners and I'll be our slave
yo useless I'm hungry
I want some chunky monkey how's about a
knuckle sandwich don't start you two who
you be both I wanna be a donkey every
family needs a dog no no way not me oh
I'm always the baby it's not fair
there's gotta be someone else I can play
according to the kids official playin
house rulebook the only parts left are
grumpy grandma pick up come on guys wait
the whole idea of playing house is to
try out the roles will be suited for
later in life so I'll play a highly
successful doctor who can buy and sell
the whole bunch of you nobody said there
was a doctor great idea Cosmo you can
give baby max his shot doggie b22 -
somebody take doggy for a walk
yo hey boats gonna need dog chow I can
run the neighborhood store oh really
then who was my kid hello I'm the mommy
remember how can I be a mommy without a
baby huh huh oh please madam let the
doctor handle this all I need is an
extra player find some kid who isn't
busy you know a loser with no friends
I'm not supposed to get upset
it makes me break out in eg hives no
wonder twos are nippy for a loser
well there's one Hey
I found him he was all by himself nobody
plays dude what's up little people look
much like a baby oh how about a pink
ribbon on his moustache he's a boy mommy
[Music]
boy you can't find anything to play with
I'll get you something how about your
little broom broom where's my kiss yes
sorry you've been kissing up to the boss
all day I'm all cursed out sit here dear
aren't you going to say hi to Daddy
oh hi your daddy you've been a good
little Godfather que tu nah he looks
awful and he smells too well that's just
his aftershave we have the only K on the
block who can grow a beard dinnertime
[Music]
touched assisted dirt our Sun is way too
picky hey Junior no cookie at the table
no picky knows no picky but just picking
up food and eat yes Daddy
no no no whoa good soup Babel what can I
use it delicious cream of mine hey sure
I feel like a but it's worth it if
it gets these little guys to relate to
me respect I've got you but I would move
much I want to put the pal in Pizza pal
I gotta keep this job or I'm out of the
witness protection program
[Music]
he's weird I mean look at that stupid
hat you made me wear this hat shin-chan
[Music]
looks constipated to me let's take him
to the doctor this guy's a quack who's a
quack you cook now I'm starting to itch
come on by Maxie bar we sell all kinds
of itching like nuts oh yeah maybe I
should just run a zoo hey Doc can you
fix this it's broken what's broken
eh crack you're such a perv oh now here
the doctor needs to be a man our baby's
not your but but but a lot better
looking than wide and say ah ah I said
open wide oh my god father crank open
that pie hole
looks bad
he needs a full exam take off his
clothes oh no really right I mean it's
just a game we're pretending so I don't
actually have to take off my you've
missed the point of this game we strive
for realism here now are you playing or
not no way to fake it you gotta get
naked pretty so what's wrong with him he
has a cold how did that happen
see what you get for running around
naked what wasn't too bright of him was
it incredibly dumb picks up your husband
home snack time everyone wash your hands
and come on I can't I'm frozen to the
stinking bench somebody bring up George
[Music]
that's the toilet seat cover
my legs just get dressed will you you're
gonna be late for school hurry I don't
want you to miss the bus again okay cuz
I am NOT riding you all the way to
school on my bike mom where the heck are
your pants mom I got a problem could you
help me of course honey what's wrong
come on tell mommy it's it
which one should I use for lunch that's
the big problem does ya ha two pairs of
chopsticks one munch do the math
mamacita huh
maybe I'll go with a master muchacho no
the second roboticle totally wrong here
use one of each
now go put on your pants before you miss
the bus
[Music]
Mitch chin I'm home sweat like satin
boonie no I'm not I got caught in the
rain
oh honey couldn't you get a cab huh in
this weather
they were all taken I need a hot shower
ah I wish I could have given him a ride
[Music]
your manager
[Applause]
[Music]
hey not that kind of ride in a car car
my horse
hmm so you want to get your driver's
license out well you would sure make our
lives a lot easier
uh-huh you think it's a good idea
driving takes a lot of patience and you
got well you know that temper tell me
about it remember when I kicked
wide-load to her butt ski yes that was
very wrong of you shin oh please you're
the one who gave me their tape she spent
the whole day at the mall without
noticing until that security guard
pulled her over for tailgating did she
go back to Rama her face was the color
of this napkin totally not this is the
one for me all good driving school local
they're cheap and they have really hot
looking um uniforms
[Music]
I want to go on the rides we're not here
to have fun
you keep driving instructors from their
brochure talk about your fault
advertising I'll leave me alone would
you like a stick shift or an automatic
hmm well I guess I want an automatic
don't give her a gun she's scary or not
automatic shift it's a car not a weapon
with you driving a car is a weapon
thanks for the support when do I start
my lessons after the written test and
that's me and my junior high production
flowery drums my drama teacher said I
could have been a big star all I needed
was talent that's nice but we need
something that's not quite so Oh
[Music]
I mean you are an old lady but my ears
still work pretty good you memorized the
booklet with this dragon test go ahead
ask you some questions okay let's see
now anything at all cuz I am ready okay
we'll start with traffic signs like this
what's this one me
[Music]
got it
don't drink and drive no you said you
studied this you mean it's wrong the ha
ha
it means slippery when wet bingo but
how'd you know even a kidney gardener
knows that maybe I should get the
license you're both crazy that roads not
wet look it's not even raining good luck
on the test no way smarty I bet I got an
a-plus unless there's a higher score
let's see so what if I don't know a
bunch of silly traffic laws most people
ignore them anyway I am going to drive
and nothing is going to stop me be very
[Music]
I'm going into driving class now
leaving but what about me I'm just me in
the next room and you're gonna play at
daycare remember will be fun
give it to me straight ma you're gonna
leave me here forever aren't you sweetie
that's not true Oh
Oh pinky swear come you maybe don't you
worry Mama's not gonna leave her boy not
ever
shin-chan najara okay ready for daycare
cool I catch these kids I feel like I'm
back into school again what a rush
excuse me Xion what sitting next to you
huh you can sit with her I'm not deaf
he's my teacher what a brainless waiting
for me
mrs. najara right I am mr. Breen your
driving instructor hi
tell me about your experience in a car
well there was that road trip last
summer my husband felt kind of frisky
and he pulled over so we get you excuse
me I don't see how that's any of your
business it's not thank God I'm aunt
have you ever driven Oh
nope guess you'll just have to teach me
lucky me get in right mrs. najara yeah
you're in the passenger seat
oh it's swear I always sit so I pretty
yeah hilarious I fear I may regret this
but get behind the wheel right now
what's the first thing you need to do
find a good radio station vitally
important of course but besides that
before you start to drive you should
always
Oh
go potty I remember one time we were
stuck in traffic and I'd had three so it
is at the mall and I thought it was
gonna explode I was so full spare me
your bathroom habits I'm talking about
your seat belt
now check the mirror idea there's no
need to fix your hair really well
super snip score is a job maybe my
grandma's Christmas party but it needs
to come fully loaded like my uncle bows
[Music]
you haven't even pulled out yet now
didn't you forget something did I oh
let's see purse
dice shake emergency kid bars have you
received a sharp blow to your head BCC
why no well you're about to release
their safety break then put your turn
signal on shift the drive step on the
gas like now slowly eyes on the road
eyes on the road sorry slowly that's
right yikes
[Music]
do a little new maybe turn which
surprised me just turned today
don't panic I'm talking to myself oh
stop turning already put in reverse
[Music]
always yield to pedestrians save watches
for instance what would you do if I were
crossing the street here give you a lift
you are one cute patootie Thanks
but what if a little old man were
crossing I tried a bit across the top
shin no even if a fat gross ugly weirdo
we're crossing what would you do keep
driving but keep my eyes shut
never mind what are you doing what are
you doing new boyfriend
huh boyfriend the shriveled up old skis
ball hit me oh um I'm so sorry I didn't
mean lessons over you fail the streets
wouldn't be safe with a ninny like you
behind the wheel
I got a cockamamie teacher on you anyway
[Music]
bacon drive yeah
[Applause]
[Music]