[Music]
scratch the head forward
now tell you answer this question right
and I won't but you all day you're on
your goes when sure you eat a hot cake
hmm ah oh it's still hot wait electric
cools or you'll burn your top I'll bury
the evidence you didn't say it was
stolen she's going hamantaschen what's
your dip you still lose I'll go play
quietly by yourself will you please I
need a nap yeah whatever just pull this
up for me first that's something else to
play with
if you say so
[Music]
I'm seeing spots all right because it's
just dirty here don't you have something
to say to me oh yeah mom maybe now I can
get a little quiet just let me sleep
will you
no more balloons in my face
[Music]
come on
be her bigger I wanted to flow me right
up to the moon not you like an express
trip
[Music]
gee samox don't you know when to quit
you kept knowing more more just a little
kid what are you listening to me for
okay I've had it the balloon pump is
closed I'll go play
no come on Richie just one more balloon
don't call me Mitzi in fact don't call
me period anyway there aren't any more
balloons oh I can find a couple couple
hundred ninis birthday party mom made me
take she made you yeah she popped an
artery trying to blow him up she's your
old drum set we made out on the deal you
can't twist a bongo to look like a
giraffe well at least they're free let's
see what we got
[Music]
[Laughter]
liar my nose caught fire I wouldn't have
enough air left to blow it out busy or
its Nucky sandwiches for lunch
[Music]
shin-chan
come here a minute huh I thought you
wanted to sleep why don't you make up
your mind even that dad couldn't sleep
in this house oh you can't beat him
Barnes over buddy that was the last of
moms air
[Music]
your house that's funny when I pledged
it at home my mom gives me cash worn-in
no let's do tire tracks on my back huh
well you have to return that wallet -
it's my floater Oh Colonel I'd keep cash
right no you can't just give it away
ja I'll take 20 pounds of chocolate
shoes don't wrap them I'll leave them
here what nobody home let's jet
sorry I'm late yeah what you cut there
you ordered noodle soup yeah like noodle
soup so you don't want if you brought
pizza maybe we talked must have got the
wrong address
[Music]
enjoy your lunch thanks a lot little boy
why did you shin-chan nohara
have we met no but the last cup on this
beach scratched your picture in his desk
with his fingernails right before they
took him away what kind of rent you pay
I don't pay rent ah freeloader huh what
do you want
oh yeah well let me have it and you can
fill out a report yeah well you slip out
the back with the dinero and head for
Vegas is worse than they said so where
exactly was the wallet I mean what road
thanks honey
you're being very helpful chunky tuna I
helped too yeah trying to be a good
boyfriend
well you are a good boy
[Music]
no you're real cute you're the cutest
handsomest fella
I ever saw okay just give me your phone
numbers I'll call you
what floor new it up K's an erv Oh pay
no I need to contact you if there's a
reward who knows the owner might be very
grateful and rich what are we waiting
for
we need return that wallet it's our duty
as honest citizens okay then
[Music]
professionals
I'll find the owner as soon as I can but
first I've got important police business
[Music]
boy what a pain lunchtime
this soup must be cold by now but I'm
starving lunch
that's your important police business I
was just about to check the wallet for
clues cool doughnuts
the money's all here see one two three
four mmm look it's a receipt this is the
perfect clue for a good detective
uh-huh too bad we don't know one let's
see plum passion lipstick scarlet dream
blush and green eyeshadow maybe it's a
married lady she also bought diet pills
breath mints my deduction is she's a
young housewife a tear on the heavy side
Hey a credit card officer I lost my
wallet
where's that Mitch Chen what are you
doing here ma'am can you tell me what
the wallet looked like yes it was bad
leather can you tell me what was in it
there was my grocery money and a credit
card and tell me your wait a hundred and
thirty five but I'm retaining water and
be a bit more careful next time your
what what do you mean oh don't tell me
he found it I'm afraid so
better pay up lady it's the LA house a
resource
kid hey glad your property they get a
ruble our next conference reprove all
right whatever
oops I found your property should not
get a reward the big city you know
grandma used to go pretty regular but
old age later constipated don't worry
dear
I'll keep Grampa out of trouble actually
I'm well okay but I'll give me one heck
of a but me very instead of Underpants
it goes on your head your head yeah cool
gags chin dude you know if I tried that
with your grandma's Underpants
it'll take rescue workers days to find
me you're gonna have your hands full mom
I think I can handle these two
characters remember I told no sir at
school for years let's do it
you're the one I'm worried about
[Music]
well I brought a thermos but you know
we're starving I don't know Senor she
sorry my favorite the kids in a big
supersized well maybe there's a forget
checkout God but in Tower one
[Music]
dang it's only grandma my eyesight must
be going oh and I don't have a hot bod
only if we borrowed you old man
don't make me unplug your pacemaker I
can't be came here to see something
uplifting I did those babes are wearing
1d bras you got corners no cash
your Social Security check let's play
something with less fruit no beach bunny
bumper cars hmm nice bumper on that
point
well you can make a geriatric jackass of
yourself I'm going to see the city with
honeyed youth
Chinchin we heard grab our space now
she's gone off on her own
what are you fed we should do well she
could get lost and wonder for hours so
before she gets back let him go
cross-eyed claim their silly video games
granny's gonna soak up a little culture
maybe I should've let her go I'm worried
helpless old lady shouldn't wander all
crammed look at that beautiful Tower oh
I forgot I ditched him or what hope he's
not too worried we should have heard
from our by now where is she huh what is
it a giant bullet here wax dinosaur
speaking of dinosaurs there's grandma
yeah you're not still mad at me are you
babe oh oh you know you can't stay mad
at me for long come on sweet lips give
me a smile your smile whoa what happens
when you ask her to give you a hand
well it's been quite a day but I think
I'm coming down with a fever Rogers we
better head home oh no babe oh it's not
that kind of fever
[Music]
[Applause]
you
[Music]