[Music]
the kids with an attitude
just scratch their homeworks
[Applause]
[Music]
talking
[Applause]
[Music]
about time you picked up my comic books
mixed I'm tired of watching you trip oh
nice job nice job
don't tie him up how can I read him you
can't see I'm pretty tired of tripping
over them myself so I'm recycling them
oh we had an agreement Shin next time
you leave your comics lying around out
oh yeah you signed a contract next time
I leave my comics lying around out there
you go my autograph it's obviously a
forgery
that's your butt say adios muchacho
okay lady get your mitts off my
muchachos you're gonna be sorry
I warned you then you should have taken
better care of them
yeah promises promises I'll be right
back I'm sorry but it's for your own
good
what are you doing my autograph Oh put
your pants on you take old comics and
that's for you
toilet paper last time you paid cash
trust me in today's economy the toilet
paper is a better deal well keep
recycling see you next time young man
next time you'll realize that what I say
I'm going to do something
shouldn't you where the heck did he go
well that's the biggest one-day hmm
[Music]
need a ride well geez pocket back here
with me manage Anna hey wrapped too
tight
you're lucky my stuff didn't go flying
all over the street your stuff
everything in that truck belongs to me
my mom forget it kid once it's in the
truck your luck
might as well save your breath oh so she
tossed your comics to teach you a lesson
it's called classic I marked all my
favorite parts with weight Gilmore I had
a favorite superhero when I was a kid
the caped
all brave man I can't believe I was ever
into that stuff muchacho quippy
rhinestone-studded panties any day you
take that back hombre rules man I had
all the hombre comics probably still
have them somewhere guess I should
recycle him but I couldn't do that to
the Cape one they wouldn't even make
good toilet paper yeah fine whatever
well I don't want muchacho comics
cluttering up my truck take him home say
would you I can have them back you gonna
leave them lying around on the floor
again no okay then don't find them I'm
recycling medals over to my house you
got a lot there think you can make it on
your own
sure yeah my own apartment if I didn't
still need my mom to tie my shoelaces I
mean can you carry those by yourself
[Music]
no way guess I better take you home
no thanks no no garyun no hey piggy as
long as you're buying
stop to take you straight home kit but
sorry Murray it's Tony
your family's probably worried about you
funny
wait no oh my gosh what was this morning
[Music]
[Applause]
sorry I was in a hurry to get him back
to you thanks sorry you caused you so
much trouble
no biggie I guess you want this back huh
no thanks toilet paper is the one thing
we don't recycle thanks for giving me my
conics back no prob kid but you better
put him away like your mom says we're
all beat back ok I'll take care of them
I promise
kids and your garbage huh thanks again
see you next time see ya see kid oh
[Music]
hello I try to get some work done time
it's always time
[Music]
they think they can make you buy
anything you just got some goofy
characters name is on it I'll go try out
my Richard Gere buster
[Music]
[Applause]
it's still not working sure hope I don't
have to call a repairman can you fix it
if you mortgage your house to pay me it
would be cheaper to buy a new TV no way
I'm fixing it myself that nosy old mrs.
ubers got child services on speed dial
[Music]
yeah might be time to call a repairman
you can fix it right I don't know lady
it might be cheaper to buy yourself a
new one
Yeah right softening me up huh well
mamacita don't fold that easy
oh come on you've seen broken TVs before
it can't be that hard to fix I gotta
tell you this one's got me stumped I
don't want to get all technical on you
so to put it in layman's terms it looks
to me like someone beat the crap out of
it you got a pet gorilla or something
you know I have been meaning to buy a
new TV
I decided to buy a brand new one first
thing tomorrow morning no you can
survive one night without TV right one
night world's most wanted ones and guns
no all the shows he's gonna miss on
television tonight
wacky car crashes mister sister that
darn alien babe watch
nicknack night on the shop till you drop
kid I married her donkey like in Spike
Seinfeld reruns all about cheese
oh I'm sorry I killed your darn TV now
what do you want from me
well it's a start
hey what's going on how the TV's not
working I'm just trying to cheer him up
a little bit what happened to the TV
we have no idea do we no not a clue
well I don't mind going without TV
tonight oh thank you can I pour you some
honey oh you want to hear what happened
in school
sure tell us all about miss Dori red
from this little square thing I think it
was called occasion I know you're here
[Music]
shin-chan darn it is that kid hiding you
shouldn't have a dog you won't take care
of it oh well I guess I have to walk you
hello oh okay how's the baby a new tooth
oh that is so adorable so what else is
new with you guys oh don't be silly
you're not interrupting anything I have
plenty of time
[Music]
you better talk to your son Harry oh boy
whatever he's my son it means he's been
flashing the neighbors again what now he
refused to walk the dog I wasn't here
why did you walk him I was busy yeah
busy on the floor how'd you know that
well you're always on the phone you were
hiding weren't you just waiting for me
to walk in if I waited that long I'd
have grown chest hey hey he's your dog
mister it's your job to walk him and
feed him I thought you were feeding him
last time you fed him around the same
time you walked in listen to you - I
can't believe this is this how you treat
man's best friend
he needs companionship not to mention a
handful of kibble now and then poor
little guy yeah you better start
treating me right where's my kibble I
don't think you heard daddy maybe if you
had
[Music]
[Applause]
walk the dog Chan Chan got one goody
left come on boy hey buddy got a new
girlfriend huh coochie coochie coochie
oh hey doesn't bug me it's a good thing
[Music]
it's like you were inside my head my dog
we-we'd in the street then he stops to
make it poo I would like to do the same
but they put me in a zoo oh I'm so sorry
sweetheart that old stuff dog was so
raggedy I didn't know I was golden it
either it out yesterday
[Music]
so your girlfriend's name is Stella
[Laughter]
[Music]
house bunny when I ate mom's leg either
[Applause]
[Music]