[Music]
parents crazy teacher scratch their
homeworks mr. Doody
[Applause]
[Music]
she crank it down just because she's
trying to defend women's right does that
threaten you Harry it has nothing to do
with women's rights somebody mentioned
women's tights it's that voice Jesus
like dragging down a blackboard
I admit it it's not a voice it's what
she has to say
whose tights yours or actual woman's it
was so typical when we have to be
treated as equals it's excuse me you
wearing women's tights I have never once
told you to shut up
but you think it's light-tight all men
like you one is a big chested little
mush brain who follows orders then I
would have married my secretary
something going on between you two are
you nuts
our relationship is strictly
professional yeah she was smuggled
awfully close in that photo from your
business retreat at Mount Fuji fun farm
she was scared of the baby mama huh so
she's brain damaged well at least that
explains why she's attracted to you I'm
not attractive you got your big hulking
toe claws at the kitchen table they fast
attractive apparently you did you're the
one who begged me to marry you that's
reaming you said I know I'm not worthy
of such an angel but I'll die without
you
yeah we're desperate
you were desperate no one man can
measure to your manly mannish manliness
I must have you does that refresh your
memory speak to me till you apologize oh
forget it you apologize to me
Shepard bags tonight that's right cool I
need a break from both your big honking
toenails
chin tell your father he can make his
own breakfast tell your mother my socks
tastes better than her eggs but don't
worry little buddy
things haven't changed between you and
your favorite parents and that would be
hurting his feelings in just tell the
truth who would you say is your favorite
parent who gives me the most right good
old dad I'm the one who brings home the
bacon
a pack of pork rinds all he can afford a
measly little paycheck I learned some
real money I can always go back to my
old career a career she were a paper hat
and said my fries with that oh no Harry
putting me down in front of my son but
it doesn't change anything a boy loves
his mother
I'm a his favorite if you think
demeaning me in front of shin is gonna
score points with a kid forget it he
respects me
I'm his favorite I feel like a piece of
meat
[Music]
where's my boy look what I got Chacho
deluxe power claw action get writing a
kid with toys well you were bribing him
with yellow dye flavored cheesy type
product at least my bribe won't make him
grow two heads so made of your mind who
your favorite parent is yet you're
moving up the charts there's no junk
food where this came from my little
Pratt's now who do you love yeah but I'm
the one who bought you this super cool
toy give you yummy treats punch come on
who do you love more just one over the
other you're right son you shouldn't
have to choose
[Music]
you know in the movies when parents
fight sometimes they split up don't
worry it always keeps the dog this whole
thing started when I couldn't say which
one's my favorite I still can't decide
so why don't you careful the one you
don't mix gonna be mad Oh Harry
he's gonna be I'll just go stay with Kay
for a while make some good points at
least my secretary thinks I'm the
world's greatest boss dad's not so bad
oh my gosh sweetheart we have a son oh
thank you
shin-chan I remember this
[Music]
Mitzi I'm sorry
Oh Harry no it was my fault the fights
over fight come on bath time want me to
wash your hair for you as you know our
student softball game is coming up and
we don't want to get an ugly right last
time I mean there was some heavy betting
on the game couple of teachers got
threatened but I promise not to do that
anymore so no pressure we're all gonna
play for fun and just to sweeten the pot
if your team wins you get a week in
Paris
[Music]
be ready for softball practice I'll hit
the ball and you catch and try to catch
it on the fly whoa that'll hurt I better
dress room a little not that kind of fly
shin-chan see the idea is to keep me
from getting the first base back off I'm
my physics tutor
he needs help understanding the time
[Music]
sorry about my desk but do me a favor
next time don't see the ball perfect
sphere she's sending you a pop fly know
what that is sure fly with a wife and
kids
listen you ignoramus we're not talking
about insects here are you crazy
[Music]
ready now shin-chan
okay we'll try again
[Music]
maybe he'll stay focused if I give him a
bat occasion ready didn't hit one out of
the park
you need to look at the picture picture
oh I don't see any pictures not in a
museum no I mean the guy with the ball
behind you see Cosmo is going to throw
it at you just like him sneak it up on
me listen stand right over here and look
at Cosmo
YAG me can't you put a bag over his head
mystery
can't we knock him up and use them for
firebase no play nice
[Music]
hey I know it's not like you're trying
to kill me but I see if she's got ties
to the scungilli family holy whoa
now I'm three minutes late this throws
my whole day off
[Music]
you losers bat first
I hear you can't hit oh I can hit while
these knuckles up your nose I ladies
maybe we should let the kids decide
who's up first let's play ball everyone
but shin you focused make the wet there
dry PYP
[Music]
Cheeta throw so fast you never see it
coming
don't swing the ball loser boy she's
only wearing to post to did a great book
I wore to the New Year's Eve party
I knew that sneak Dorie had a camera
[Music]
I know it looked like a total boob but
as long as she gets the signal if I
might interject her it might be more
effective to holler hey dum-dum really
gonna get ugly face breakdance you
coming on to me I'm giving you secret
signals you pointy-headed catch a clue
Sport she's giving you a secret message
mmm what's the secret Steele did you
even hear what I said sure my mistake
a nice loincloth your mom noticed too
can't missing yeah I'm getting pretty
good for this ventriloquist dummy why
I'm seeing beer barrel polka
[Music]
[Applause]
we're going down the tube strat the
Cheetahs yeah boohoo he'll be sliding
into home before your tears are even dry
steal third
[Music]
hey so you didn't strike him out it's
not the end of the world yeah don't
think you have to win this game on your
own remember you're part of a team a
team pulls together on my own
[Music]
bring out the relief pitcher oddball no
Hara you're hanging this on shin-chan
trust me
we call him oddball for a reason yeah
cuz he drops trou
[Music]
fugitive was hard on the nerves
[Applause]
[Music]