[Applause]
it starts with one thing i don't know
why it doesn't even matter how hard you
tried keep that in mind i designed this
right to explain in due
know time is a valuable thing watch it
fly by as the pendulum swings watch it
count down to the end of the day the
clock takes life away it's so unreal
didn't look out hello watch the time go
right out the window trying to hold on
to didn't even know i wasted it all just
to watch you go i kept everything inside
and even though i tried it all fell
apart what it meant to be will
eventually be a memory of a time i tried
so hard
but in the end
[Applause]
[Music]
way you were mocking me acting like i
was part of your property remembering
all the times you fought with me i'm
surprised it got lost so things aren't
the way they were before you wouldn't
even recognize me anymore not that you
knew me back then but it all comes back
to me indeed
you kept everything inside and even
though i tried it all fell apart what it
meant to me will eventually be a memory
of a time when i tried so high
but in the end it doesn't even matter
[Applause]
i'll put my trust
in you
just as far as i can go
for all this if there's only one thing
you should know
i've put my trust
in you
pushed as far as i can go
for all this there's only one thing you
should know
i tried so hard
it doesn't even matter
[Applause]
[Music]
you