[Music]
i'm peppa pig
this is my little brother george
this is mummy pig
and this is daddy pig
baby alexander
pepper and george's cousins are coming
to visit today
mummy how long before cousin chloe is
here not long now peppa baby alexander
is coming too remember oh babies cry all
the time they're so noisy i'm sure baby
alexander won't be that noisy
what's that sound is it a car alarm is
this a fire engine
no it's baby alexander
hello george hello
hello everyone hello uncle pig hello
hello auntie pig you remember baby
alexander don't you peppa
are you staying for a few days no this
is what alexander needs for just one day
can't go anywhere without all these baby
things oh
hello baby alexander he can't talk peppa
if he can't talk then how do you know
what he wants we guess
i'm guessing he's hungry peppa would you
like to help feed alexander yes please
[Music]
it is lunch time for baby alexander
cousin peppa is going to feed you today
alexander here you are baby
oh
here it is
he keeps turning his head feeding baby
alexander is quite hard watch this here
comes the aeroplane
alexandra likes it if you pretend the
spoon is an aeroplane you have a gold
pepper
here comes the aeroplane
open your
that was an aeroplane can you say
aeroplane
i told you he can't talk he hasn't even
said his first word yet peppa do you
remember what your first word was no
it was
mummy
i thought peppa's first word was daddy
no mommy
what was george's first word i saw
george's first word was dinosaur
somebody looks like they had a good
lunch yes bath time i think
baby alexander is having a bath
this is mr dinosaur can you say dinosaur
go go
he can't talk peppa but he will talk one
day then you'll know what he wants
what do you want to do now alexander
i think he wants to go for a walk he
can't walk yet but he can go out in his
buggy
[Music]
that's a clever little buggy yes five
gears mudguards and abs as standard
blah that's how daddies talk
alexander likes it when you talk peppa
that's because i am very interesting
this is the sky can you say sky go go
the sky is where rain comes from can you
say rain
rain is good for ducks and plants and
making
i love jumping up and down in puddles
hot dolls
alexander has said his first word
puddles
[Music]
and i taught him to say it
puddles
[Music]
you