[Music]
chris gardner
chris gardner how are you
good morning chris gardner
chris garner good to see you again chris
gardner pleasure
i've been sitting out there for the last
half hour trying to come up with a story
that would explain my being here
dressed like this and and i wanted to
come up with a story
that would demonstrate qualities that
i'm sure you all admire here like
like earnestness or diligence and
team playing to something and i couldn't
think
of anything so the truth is
i was arrested for failure to pay
parking tickets parking figures
and i ran all the way here from the the
polk station the police station
what were you doing before you were
arrested i was uh
painting my apartment did you dry now
i hope so jay says you're pretty
determined
oh he's been waiting outside the front
of the building with some 40-pound gizmo
for over a month
he said you're smart i'd like to think
so
and you want to learn this business yes
sir i want to learn this business
have you already started learning on
your own absolutely
jay yes sir how many times have you seen
chris
no i don't know one too many apparently
has he ever dressed like this no no
jacket and ty
first in your class in school
high school yes sir how many in the
class
uh 12. it was a small town
i'll say but i was also first in my
radar class
in in the navy and that was a class of
20.
can i say something um
i'm the type of person if you ask me a
question
and i don't know the answer i'm gonna
tell you that i don't know
but i bet you what i know how to find
the answer
and i will find the answer
is that fair enough chris
what would you say if a guy walked in
for an interview without a shirt on and
i
hired him what would you say
he must have had on some really nice
pants
chris i don't know how you did it
dressed as a garbage man but you really
pulled it off in there thank you very
much mr twistle hey now you can call me
jay
all right we'll talk to you soon thanks
uh i'll let you know jay
you'll you'll let me know jay what do
you mean yeah i'll give you a call
tomorrow
sometime and wait what what are you
talking you hounded me for this you
stood here
listen there's no salary no i was not
aware of that
my circumstances have changed some and i
need to be certain
that i'll be able to okay
tonight i swear i will fill your spot i
promise
you i'll look like if you back out you
know what i'll look like to the partners
yes
and ass
an ass all the way
you are a piece of work
tonight
you